Choyo Matsuta

Home Address Harbor City, CA 90710, USA Cell (714) 875-7913

Email cmatsuta@hotmail.com

Summary

Professional ERP consultant and system architect who has ability to assist in designing ERP business software systems. Hands on experience in operations using Microsoft ERP system such as Dynamics GP and Dynamics 365 FO, BC and Sales, Power platform and also implementing Shopify API. Have the necessary expertise to develop business and accounting software to help facilitate the business operations of clients. Will to consult with engineering stuff to evaluate interface between hardware and software, develop specifications and performance requirements and resolve customer problems.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Japan Business Systems Technology Torrance, CA Sep., 2011 - Current Sr ERP System Consultant / Assistant Manager

- · Configure fully integrated ERP system for over 50 companies
- Conducted ERP business assessment and requirement analysis as project leader.
- Assisted customers to solve issues related with ERP system and related modules.
- Maintained and coordinated proposed designs for ERP system releases.
- · Lead new functions and features and help improving team skills.

Calsoft Systems, Torrance, CA Nov., 2009 - Sep., 2011

Accounting Operation Support

- Assisted internal accounting and operation tasks.
- Assisted manager with closing process and prepared monthly Work in Progress reports.
- Provided high quality helpdesk support by troubleshoot telephonically or emailing with customers in both English and Japanese and document help desk requests and resolutions.
- Create or revise user instructions, procedures, or manuals.
- Prepared training and workflow documentations.
- Test developed software.

EDUCATION

UCR Extension Web development, July 2020 - Current

Activities and Societies: The Coding Boot Camp at UCR Extension covers a full-stack curriculum, including HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, jQuery, Bootstrap, Express.js, React.js, Node.js, Database Theory, MongoDB, MySQL, Command Line, Git, and more.

Bachelor of Arts - Business Administration, May 2008

Major: Accounting

California State University, Fullerton, CA

Bachelor of Science - Business Administration, May 2006

Grossmont College, El Cajon, CA

RELEVANT COURSEWORK

Links to deployed app: https://cmatsuta.github.io/myportfolio/portfolio.html

RECOGNITIONS

Recognized as an outstanding CSUF student July 2006.

SKILLS

Languages:

Speak, read and write English and Japanese

Other:

Active communication skills

Ability to interact with a wide variety of cultures

Teamwork and ability to relate to and lead people

Motivate, hardworking, and reliable

Ability to contribute and convey thoughts and ideas to others effectively

Commented [1]: Great job providing contact details and links to sites. This is important as it introduces you correctly as well as provides links to resources if the reader wants to learn more.

This section should also provide links to your LinkedIn, GitHub, and portfolio.

Also, It is the current best practice to omit street addresses from the resume. This is considered unnecessary at this point in the hiring process (only city, state, and postal code are needed).

Commented [2]: Make sure to introduce yourself in your desired/target role.

For example:

Front-End Web Developer leveraging a background in psychology to build a more intuitive user experience on the web. Recently earned a certificate in Full Stack Development from the University of Central Florida, with newly developed skills in JavaScript, CSS, React, is, and responsive web design. Known as an innovative problem-solver passionate about developing apps, with a focus on mobile-first design and development. With each project, my aim is to best engage my audience for an impactful user-experience. I applied aspects of UX and agile development in a recent project where I worked in a team of four to develop a single-page MERN app that helps local

Commented [3]: Great job getting started with your job descriptions as you provide valuable content to help develop your descriptions further!
Provide 2 to 3 bullet points highlighting accomplishments rather than day-to-day tasks. This template makes it easy to develop each bullet point. This is very important as we want to showcase your success in your job duties and stand out above the rest

Commented [4]: Certificate in Full Stack Web Development, UCR Extension, END/DATE

Commented [5]: Your Projects section is missing links to your code and deployed applications. The Projects section is a very important part of your technical resume. Recruiters use this section to gauge your ability for the role that they are filling. Be sure that each project has the same structure of content. I suggest the following structure:

Project Name | Link to Github | Link to Deployed

Commented [6]: Modern tech resumes consist of five sections: summary, skills, projects, education and experience. The reason is to be focused and concise to maximize the 7 to 10 seconds it takes for a prospective employer to make a decision about you. Please move the content in this section to your LinkedIn profile.

Commented [7]: This section should be renamed Technical Skills and include ONLY tech skills.

Here are a list of the skills pertaining to your program. Review this list to ensure you have included all that apply to you. Don't add skills to add them. You want to add those that you can talk about comfortably in an interview.

C	ua	lifica	tions	Sum	marv

Microsoft Dynamics AX Financials, Microsoft Dynamics AX Trade and Logistics, Microsoft Dynamics GP Integration Manager, Microsoft Dynamics GP Financials

Commented [8]: This section should not be included.